{
    "subject": "Jacques_Feyder",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Le_Grand_Jeu__1934_film_",
    "human_readable": "Jacques Feyder created the film Le Grand Jeu (1934).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8996579647064209,
            "question": "Who created the film Le Grand Jeu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.88798588514328,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Jacques Feyder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8083358407020569,
            "question": "How might the film Le Grand Jeu have been received by audiences in 1934?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.690765917301178,
            "question": "What year was the film Le Grand Jeu released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4505980908870697,
            "question": "Is Le Grand Jeu a fictional or non-fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43027496337890625,
            "question": "Were there any notable actors involved in Le Grand Jeu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4292542338371277,
            "question": "What genre is the film Le Grand Jeu likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38741976022720337,
            "question": "Can you name any other films directed by Jacques Feyder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34702301025390625,
            "question": "What might be some common themes explored in a film from 1934?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1373291313648224,
            "question": "What were the typical cinematic styles of the 1930s?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jacques Feyder created the film Le Grand Jeu (1934).",
            "html": "yago_8595_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might be some common themes explored in a film from 1934?",
            "html": "yago_8595_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any other films directed by Jacques Feyder?",
            "html": "yago_8595_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Le Grand Jeu likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_8595_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8595_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8595_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8595_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8595_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8595_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8595_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8595_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8595_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8595_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8595_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states: \"Jacques Feyder's sole directorial contribution in 1934... was the superior Foreign Legion melodrama *Le Grand Jeu*\".  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports Jacques Feyder as the director of the film \"Le Grand Jeu\" released in 1934."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}